

**Farid Ismavilov** 

**DOB:** 18.08.1989 **MOB:** +994513804066 **Email:** ismayilov.ferid55@gmail.com

Seasoned leader with 10 + years of experience in hotels' industry. Started hotel career in 2008 and shaped up my career to fit my objectives. (I Don't aim for job; I aim for career). Able to achieve outstanding results, due to expertise in the areas of:

Operations Management
Sales & Business Development
Customer Relationship Management
Opera PMS / Concerto
Up selling & Annual Target planning

Performance Metrics Analyze
Overbooking Management Team
Training Arrangement Logbook
Comment Reports for GM Verbal
Written Communication

## **Education**

Azerbaijan Tourism and Hotel Management University

2006 - 2010

**Azerbaijan** 

Hotel Management

\_

## **Experience**

Intercontinental Hotels Group / StayBridge Suites Baku **Hotel Manager (Reliever of General Manager)** 

Intercontinental Hotels Group / StayBridge Suites Doha **Guest Services Manager / Operations in Charge** 

Intercontinental Hotels Group / StayBridge Suites Baku

Rooms Division Manager

Intercontinental Hotels Group / StayBridge Suites Baku **Pre-Opening Front Desk Manager & Duty Manager** 

Hilton Baku

**Night Manager** 

Hilton Dubai Jumeirah

**Front Office Supervisor** 

Hilton Abu Dhabi

**Front Office Receptionist** 

Wellington Heights Hotel

**Guest Service Agent** 

Royal Beach Hotel

Hotel Management Trainee / F&B and FO Operation

Adam & Eva Hotel

Hotel Management Trainee / F&B and FO Operations

Excelsior Hotel

**Hotel Management Trainee / F&B and FO Operations** 

Baku, Azerbaijan **Since January 2020** 

Doha, Qatar

May 2019 - January 2020 (8 months)

Baku, Azerbaijan

June 2017 - May 2019 (2 years)

Baku, Azerbaijan

February2016 - June 2017 (1 year 3 months)

Baku, Azerbaijan

December 2014 - December 2015 (1 Year)

Dubai, UAE

June 2013-December 2014 (1 Year 6 months)

Abu Dhabi, UAE

February 2012 - June 2013 (1 Year 4 months)

Baku, Azerbaijan

**July 2011 – February 2012 (6 months)** 

Eilat, Israel

2009 (February – October/7 months)

Antalya, Turkey

2008 (May - September / 5 months)

Baku, Azerbaijan

2008 (January - May / 4 months)

## **Personal Particulars**

Languages: Fluent in English, Russian, Turkish, Azerbaijani & basic Arabic

<u>Interests and Hobbies:</u> Travelling, Chess, Biking.

<u>Availability</u>: 3 weeks' Notice Period Address: Po Box 1000, Baku, Azerbaijan